JASON RIVERA

Portfolio LinkedIn GitHub Email Mobile jasonrivera.xyz linkedin.com/rivera-jason github.com/jason-rivera jrivera14@my.bcit.ca (778) 580-7238

EDUCATION

Computer Systems Technology Diploma, BCIT Graduating Dec 2022 GPA – 89%

TECHNICAL

- Java
- JavaScript
- HTML
- CSS
- API (learning)
- React (learning)
- SQL (learning)
- C (learning)
- GitHub
- Google Firebase
- Agile Methodology

FUN FACTS

- Basketball Player
- World Traveler
- Avid Cyclist
- Aspiring YouTuber

PROFILE

I am a highly motivated and enthusiastic student in the computer systems technology program at BCIT. I am committed to ongoing collaboration and self-improvement. I have a first term GPA of 89%. I am adaptable and able to meet changing job requirements quickly, as demonstrated by my work experience.

PROJECTS

Tutor Finder, Projects 1 Course

Sept 2020 – Dec 2020

- Worked in a team of 3 using the Agile development process to develop a web app that allows tutors and students to connect online during the pandemic.
- Implemented the login, user profile, and search pages which pulls information from the database.

Technologies: JavaScript, HTML, CSS, GitHub, Firebase, Bootstrap

Amiibo Finder, Personal Project

Jan 2020

- Developed a web app that pulls character information from the Amiibo API and displays them to the user.
- Taught myself about APIs in my free time during school.

Technologies: API, JavaScript, HTML, CSS

DisConvo, nwHacks Hackathon

Jan 2020

- Developed a web app with 3 teammates that matches users of opposing views to discuss different topics.
- Implemented a familiar user interface.

Technologies: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, GitHub

EXPERIENCE

Server

Mar 2018 – Dec 2020

Joey Restaurant

- Communicated clearly and effectively with guests and staff in order to maintain high quality service.
- Trained new staff, providing demonstrations and answering questions.

Manager

July 2016 - Aug 2018

Caffe Artigiano

- Duties such as ordering, scheduling, hiring, and training and increased sales by 20% by the end of my tenure.
- Communicated clearly and effectively with upper management and suppliers via email.